One day, as a
medical student, I woke up and knew that today at my
university we were going to a
health clinic, so I got ready and made
my breakfast.  And no, it's not an
internship, we were just doing a
project about painting exhibitions.  We
spoke with several families and it was great
.  So, to make it clear that this
wasn't an internship, we weren't
attending to anyone.  And then I came back,
went straight to lunch with my family, and got ready
, guys, so I could get
my lips touched up, which takes an
hour to get there and an hour to get back.
It's very far, so it took me too long.
I got home, it was already kind of late,
I spent some time with my sister, had
an afternoon coffee and
rested a bit so I could go to the gym.
Guys, I ate something before the gym,
met up with Lelê, and we're off to work out.
Quadriceps workout, plus 30 minutes on the
stairs.  I went back home, had dinner, and saw what
my mom was doing, guys.
Right after that I took a nice hot shower,
called Kauan, and went to sleep.